<Gump closable="true" disposable="true" dragable="false" resizable="true">
	<VBox padding="16" backgroundID="3600" FitToContents="true">
		<Label hue="1153">"World Open Capture the Flag Event Instructions"</Label>
		<Label hue="1153">"YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR THIS INFO!"</Label>
		<Label hue="1153">"BE SURE TO SCROLL DOWN TO READ IT ALL!"</Label>
		<Label hue="1153">"If you page about something that is clearly"</Label>
		<Label hue="1153">"answered here, we will not be happy!"</Label>
		<HTML hasbackground="true" scrollbar="true" width="400" height="290">
			<basefont color="#000000">
			<p>This is a globally open capture the flag competition. Please read the instructions carefully.</p>
			<p>Teams for this event are randomly assigned.</p>
			<p>During the actual event, you will NOT actually be playing your own character. You will be given the option of choosing a character template. Reagents are not required to cast spells and basic supplies (exceptional armor, weapons, lesser cure and refresh potions) are provided to you. If you die, you will be given the option to rejoin the event as another character template (There is no penalty, BUT the number of "lives" you use is tracked and may be reported even though it will not affect your score for the purposes of the competition). During this event, Energy Vortex and Summoning spells are disabled! <u>AssistUO DOES NOT WORK with this event, so use Razor!</u></p>
			<p>You may communicate with your team members by pressing comma for team chat (e.g. typing ",hello" will send "hello" to your team)</p>			
			<p><basefont color="#ff0000">THE GOAL</basefont> is to capture the enemy team's flag. To do this, simply run over it and then bring it back to your base and run over your flag's tile. Your flag must be in your base for you to capture the flag! If you die while carrying another team's flag, your teammates can run over it to pick it up or the enemy team can run over it to return it to their base.</p>
			<p>This event will last for 30 minutes.</p>
			<p>If the capture the flag map is bounded by a particular area, then running out of bounds will result in death.</p>
			<p>You are unable to harm your teammates.</p>
			<p><u>REGARDING YOUR CLIENT VERSION</u></p>
			<p>IF you are not using client version 7.0.15.1 (the one supported by UO Forever), there is a possibility that you will run into problems with this event (it has not been tested). It is highly recommended that you download the FULL CLIENT installer from uoforever.com. NOTE that you CAN have more than 1 client installed on your computer at once and can simply switch between them by changing the client location in the Razor startup screen.</p>
			</basefont>
		</HTML>
		<HBox>
			<Button normalID="5540" pressedID="5542" name="templateShowScreen"/>
			<Label hue ="1553">"Show me the available templates."</Label>
		</HBox>
		<Spacer height="10"/>
		<HBox>
			<Label hue ="1553">"Registration Fee:"</Label>
			<Label hue ="38">xmlints.teamRegistrationCost</Label>
		</HBox>
		<HBox>
			<Button normalID="5540" pressedID="5542" name="registerTeam"/>
			<Label hue ="1553">"Register for this Event"</Label>
		</HBox>
	</VBox>
</Gump>